https://www.yandy.com/privacy-policy

CYBER MONDAY! 1200+ ITEMS ON SALE!Need Help?
800.883.0860   or  Contact UsSTANDARDPLUS SIZESearch Yandy
navigationSearchMy AccountFavoritesCart STANDARDPLUS SIZE
Lingerieview Lingerie menu Accessoriesview Accessories menu Clothingview Clothing menu Brasview Bras menu Hosieryview Hosiery menu Pantiesview Panties menu Dancewearview Dancewear menu Swimwearview Swimwear menu Shoesview Shoes menu Costumesview Costumes menu Sale!view Sale! menu Plus Size Lingerieview Plus Size Lingerie menu Plus Size Swimwearview Plus Size Swimwear menu Plus Size Dressesview Plus Size Dresses menu Plus Size Brasview Plus Size Bras menu Plus Size Hosieryview Plus Size Hosiery menu Plus Size Pantiesview Plus Size Panties menu Plus Size Clothingview Plus Size Clothing menu Plus Size Costumesview Plus Size Costumes menuMy AccountFavorites
Search
Yandy Privacy PolicyEffective Date: 03/05/2020Last Updated: 03/05/2020This Privacy Policy describes how Yandy.com (“Yandy.com”, “Yandy”, “Yandy LLC”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) collects, uses, and shares personal information of users of this website, www.yandy.com (the “Site”). We periodically update this Privacy Policy and reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy or our privacy practices at any time. We encourage you to review this site periodically and we will alert you that changes have been made by updating the Effective Date of the Policy. Your use of the Site constitutes consent to any changes in this Policy as in effect on the date of such use.ONLINE PRIVACY—THE INFORMATION WE GATHER. The type of information we gather online falls into one of the general categories: Aggregate Site Usage Information, Online Order Information, Voluntary Registered Shopper Information, Click-Stream DataAGGREGATE SITE USAGE INFORMATION. We collect and store information about the pages viewed by all of our website visitors. We then use this data in aggregate form to identify overall visitor behavior patterns. Our goal in using this information is to improve our site by making it more responsive to the needs and preferences of our users. Our Web servers automatically collect information about each visitor who requests Yandy.com Web pages, including your computer's internet protocol (IP) address. This IP address allows us to identify your computer on the internet so that the Web content you request from us can be sent to you. From time to time, we may provide portions of this aggregate site behavior information to vendors, consultants, potential advertisers or news agencies. We typically do this in order to demonstrate the amount of interest in our sites and/or to plan for technical infrastructure improvements.ONLINE ORDER INFORMATION. If you choose to purchase products from the Yandy.com site, we require the following information in order to fulfill your order: We request an e-mail address during the order process so that we can send an e-mail confirmation message acknowledging the receipt of your order. This message contains your name, address, Yandy.com membership number (if applicable), the list of items you purchased, an order reference number, a confirmation of your shipping method, and the total amount of items requested. Please note that this confirmation e-mail does NOT contain your credit card number.CLICK-STREAM DATA (AND COOKIE TECHNOLOGY). In order to register on-or purchase products from-Yandy.com websites, your browser must be set to accept "cookies." A cookie is a small piece of data housed in a text file or folder on your computer's hard drive that helps us recognize you when you visit our sites. We use cookies to help us remember things such as the following: (1) the profile facts you tell us about yourself, (2) your specified areas of interest on our sites, (3) the items you've placed in your shopping basket, and/or (4) the pages you visit as you shop. The only personal information our Yandy.com cookie can contain is information that you supply yourself. Our cookies cannot read data from other parts of your computer. If you would like more technical information about how cookies work, take a look at http://www.cookiecentral.com. As stated above, you must enable cookies on your Web browser for Yandy.com to function correctly. If you are concerned about information contained in your Yandy.com cookie, you may delete the file(s) at the end of each browser session. View your browser's help file for more information on cookies. Click-stream data is information that describes the page-by-page paths you take as you browse through our websites. Using cookies, we track and store this information to help us positively customize your shopping experience. We may use click-stream data in the aggregate to provide improved services to groups of shoppers who behave similarly. We may also use it on an individual basis to improve your specific shopping experience.COMMUNICATIONS FROM YANDY.COM. Whenever you purchase products from Yandy.com, sign up for our newsletter, or any of our on site promotions, we collect and store the information that you volunteer. Information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address and phone number. The information you supply is added to our customer database. You may receive periodic printed or e-mail communications from us about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events. You will not receive any phone calls from us unless there is a customer service issue. In some instances, we use third-party companies, like Twilio, to help us provide products and services to you, to assist us in managing customer information, or to fulfill our in house promotions and communicate with you. Some of these companies are given access to your contact information. These companies are contractually restricted from using your information in any manner other than in the service we have contracted them to do. Our customers privacy is very important to us. To learn more about Twilio’s privacy practices, please visit their website at https://www.twilio.com/legal/privacy.If you want to be removed from all Yandy.com marketing, choose one of the following options: Send an e-mail and type REMOVE FROM ALL MARKETING in the subject line; call 800-883-0860 Send your request by mail to Yandy.com Membership Services, 21615 N. 7th Ave. Phoenix, AZ 85027 Remember to include your name, address, membership number (if applicable) and phone number in the request.CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS. If you are a California Consumer, you have certain rights with respect to the collection, use, transfer, and processing of your “Personal Information”, as defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA). We reserve the right to limit these rights where permitted under applicable law, including where your identity cannot be reasonably verified or to the extent your rights adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others. To exercise any of the rights below, please contact us via the contact information below. Only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information.Collection of Personal InformationWhen California Consumers access the Yandy websites, use Yandy services, purchase our products, or contact Yandy, we collect the following Personal Information. Categories of consumer’s Personal Information collectedExamplesBusiness or commercial purposes for which the information was collectedCategories of sources from which that information was collectedCategories of third parties with whom the business shares personal informationIdentifiersReal Name, Alias, Post Address, Email, Phone number.Process your transactions.Provide you with the products you request.Communicate with you regarding your account or transactions with us.Send you offers and promotions for our products and services.This information is collected directly from you.Affiliates, analytics providers, service providers, transactions processors, IT vendors, and law enforcement (if necessary).Financial InformationCredit Card InformationProcess your transactions.This information is collected directly from you.Affiliates, analytics providers, service providers,transactions processors, IT vendors, and law enforcement (if necessary).Commercial InformationPurchases obtained or considered.Provide you with the products you request.Process your transactions.This information is collected directly fromyou or by logging our interactions with you.Affiliates, analytics providers, service providers,transactions processors, IT vendors, and law enforcement (if necessary).Internet or Electronic Network Activity InformationBrowsing history, information regarding a consumer’sinteraction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement,internet Protocol address, device ID,cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad Identifiers.Provide you with targeted advertising based on your activity on our sites. Operate, understand, optimize, develop, or improve our sites,applications, products, services and operations.Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.Investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies.We collect your internet or other electronic network activity information from your interactions with our website.Affiliates, analytics providers, service providers,transactions processors, IT vendors, and law enforcement (if necessary).In the preceding 12 months, we have not sold Personal Information about consumers. In the preceding 12 months, we have not sold Personal Information about minors.Individual RightsRight to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, or SoldYou have the right to request that Yandy disclose the Personal Information it collects, uses, and discloses about you to third parties. There are two types of Right to Know requests you can make:  1. Right to Know (Abbreviated Request): If you make a Right to Know (Abbreviated Request), you will receive the following information about you:    a. Category of personal information collected,     b. Categories of sources from which that information was collected,     c. The business or commercial purpose(s) for which the information was collected,    d. The categories of third parties to whom Yandy sold or disclosed the category of personal information for a business purpose, and    e. The business or commercial purpose for which Yandy sold or disclosed the category of personal information.  2. Right to Know (Specific Pieces of Information Request): If you make a Right to Know (Specific Pieces of Information Request), you will receive the following information about you:    a. Specific pieces of Personal Information collected about you. Yandy does not sell any Personal Information of California consumers. This information will be provided to you free of charge, unless Yandy determines that your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive. You may request this information twice in a 12-month period. Right of DeletionYou have the right to request that Yandy and our service providers delete any Personal Information about yourself that Yandy has collected from you upon receipt of a verifiable request. This right is subject to exceptions.Submitting RequestsYou can submit your request by calling us at 800-883-0860. You may also submit a request through a webform available by emailing us at service@yandy.com.Verifying RequestsYandy provides California Consumers with the ability to submit requests through our request website, our telephone number, and our email address. Yandy must verify that the person requesting information or deletion is the California Consumer about whom the request relates in order to process the request.
To verify a California Consumer’s identity, we may request up to up to three pieces of Personal Information about you when you make a request to compare against our records.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information if we cannot verify your identity.Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us.
We will only use Personal Information provided in your request to verify your identity and will delete any information you provide after processing the request.
Yandy reserves the right to take additional steps as necessary to verify the identity of California Consumers where we have reason to believe a request is fraudulent.Authorized AgentYou may choose a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf to submit your requests (“Authorized Agent”). If you choose to use an Authorized Agent, Yandy requires that you provide the Authorized Agent with written permission to allow them to submit your request and that you verify your identity directly with Yandy. Failure to do so may result in Yandy denying your request.Right to Equal ServiceYandy will not discriminate against you because you exercised any of your rights, including, but not limited to, by:  • Denying goods or services to you.  • Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties.  • Providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you.  • Suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.EUROPEAN UNION USERS. This section of our Privacy Policy provides certain required information to persons located in the European Union (“EU”), a European Economic Area (“EAA”) member state, or Switzerland. Before Yandy collects any Personal Data from you, you are entitled under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), to the information in this section of our Privacy Policy.Purposes and Legal Bases for Processing Personal DataYandy will only process your “Personal Data,” as defined by the GDPR, for lawful purposes under the GDPR that are related to Yandy’s business purposes and arising from your relationship with Yandy. Yandy will ordinarily collect and process your Personal Data because it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or because Yandy has another legitimate interest in doing so.
When Yandy cannot rely on either of such legal grounds, we will seek your prior consent.Our legitimate interests include but are not limited to:Provide you with the products and services you request, view, engage with, or purchase;Communicate with you regarding your account or transactions with us; andOperate, understand, optimize, develop, or improve our sites, applications, products, services and operations. Rights of Users Located in the EUIf you use the websites and are located in the EU, EAA, or Switzerland, you are entitled by law to access, correct, amend, or delete Personal Data about you that we hold. A list of these rights is below. Please note that these rights are not absolute and certain exemptions apply. The right to access. You have the right to ask us for copies of your Personal Data. This right has some exemptions, which means you may not always receive all the Personal Data we collect and process. When making a request, please provide an accurate description of the Personal Data to which you want access.The right to rectification. You have the right to ask us to rectify information you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.The right to erasure. You have the right to ask us to erase your Personal Data in certain circumstances, including: (i) when your Personal Data is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or processed, or (ii) your Personal Data must be erased to comply with a legal obligation under EU Union or Member State law.The right to restrict processing. You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances, including: (i) when the accuracy of the Personal Data is brought into question, or (ii) when we no longer need the Personal Data for purposes of the processing but you require such Personal Data for the establishment, exercise, or defense of a legal claim. The right to data portability. You have the right to ask that we transfer the Personal Data you gave us from one organization to another, or give it to you.The right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority. If you believe your rights under the GDPR have been violated, the GDPR gives you the right to file a complaint with the supervisory authority. A list of Supervisory Authorities is available here:
http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm.The right to withdraw consent. If Yandy obtains your written consent to collect and process your Personal Data, you can subsequently withdraw such consent as to any further processing of information by contacting us at 800-883-0860. To exercise these rights please contact us at 800-883-0860. For your protection, we may need to verify your identity before responding to your request. In the event that we refuse a request, we will provide you a reason as to why.Right to Object to ProcessingYou have the right to object to the processing of your Personal Data that is based on legitimate interests. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the Personal Data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or we can demonstrate the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. You can object to the processing of your Personal Data by contacting us at 800-883-0860.Cross-Border Transfers of Personal DataPersonal data that you provide while in the EU, an EAA member state, or Switzerland will be transferred to the United States. The GDPR permits such transfer when necessary for the performance of a contract between you and Yandy, if Yandy obtains your explicit consent to such transfer, or if it is Yandy’s legitimate interest to transfer the Personal Data.
The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. However, when transferring Personal Data to and processing Personal Data in the United States, we will obtain your consent before making any transfers of data. Retention of Your Personal Data We will retain your Personal Data until the Personal Data is no longer necessary to accomplish the purpose for which it was provided. We may retain your Personal Data for longer periods for specific purposes to the extent that we are obliged to do so in accordance with applicable laws and regulations, to protect you, other people, and us from fraud, abuse, an unauthorized access, as necessary to protect our legal rights, or for certain business requirements. YOUR RIGHTS TO ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. You have the right to access personal information about you that Yandy has collected through this Site by sending a request for access to service@yandy.com. You can also request that we correct or delete any such information by choosing one of the following options: Send an e-mail to service@yandy.com and type REMOVE FROM ALL MARKETING in the subject line; call 800-883-0860; Send your request by mail to Yandy.com Membership Services, 21615 N. 7th Ave. Phoenix, AZ 85027 Remember to include your name, address, membership number (if applicable) and phone number in the request. To verify that the request is authentic, we may require that such request be sent from the email address or billing address associated with your personal information. While we will comply reasonably and promptly with your request, we may need to retain some of your information for our own record keeping or to fulfill a legal obligation.OTHER PRIVACY NOTES. Yandy.com may provide links to websites outside of Yandy.com as an added convenience to the user. There are also affiliates that link to Yandy.com. Any link included does not imply or convey endorsement of the other company or organization, its site, or its products or services. Yandy.com is not responsible for the privacy, terms of use, or other policies of any other website.CHILDREN'S POLICY. We do not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from children through our websites. Please do not allow children under the age of 13 to provide any personally identifiable information or participate in the bulletin board sections of Yandy.com websites.CONTACT US. If you have any questions, please contact us at:Call: 800-883-0860Email: service@yandy.comGET10% OFF!HEY BABES! SIGNUP TO OUR EXCLUSIVE E-MAIL LIST AND GET 10% OFF YOUR FIRST ORDER
Instagram
Facebook
Twitter
PinterestCustomer CareTrack OrderReturn AuthorizationFrequently Asked QuestionsContact YandyAbout Yandy BlogPrivacy Policy CareersShopLingeriePlus Size LingerieCheap LingerieSexy DressesSexy Halloween CostumesGift Cards(*) Discount for first-time subscribers only. Select brands & items already on sale are excluded. By texting 300300, you are consenting to receive texts from Yandy Mobile Alerts that may be sent by an automatic telephone dialing system. 6 msgs/month. Consent is not required as a condition of any purchasing goods or services. Messages will be sent to the mobile number used at opt-in. Privacy Policy: Click here. For SMS Terms & Conditions Click here. Message & data rates may apply. Text HELP for help. Text STOP to quit
Shop By CategoryShop All LingerieBodyshapersBabydollsBedroom CostumesBodystockingsBodysuitsBra & Panty SetsBridal LingerieBustiersCamisole SetsChemisesCorsetsCrotchless LingerieGarter BeltsGarter LingerieGownsPajamas & SleepwearRobesSilk & Satin LingerieTeddiesVinyl & Latex LingerieUltra Sexy LingerieMen's Lingerie
Trending ShopsPlayboy Speakeasy CollectionHoliday Lingerie2020 Holiday Gift GuideYandy Exclusive LingerieWork From Home WardrobeYandy Vixens ShopYandy 101: The Ultimate Guide
Shop By CategoryBody StickersBreast EnhancersCapesCostume AccessoriesCostume MakeupCostume MasksCostume PropsEye MasksFace MasksFalse EyelashesFestival AccessoriesHair AccessoriesHandcuffsJewelryLeg WarmersLight Up AccessoriesPastiesRave AccessoriesWhipsWigs
Shop All Clothing Shop New Dresses Shop Sale Clothing Shop Sale Dresses
TrendingDenimSummer ClothingWet Look & Leather ClothingHigh Waisted Clothing DressesClub DressesDancewear DressesCocktail DressesLittle Black DressesMini DressesMaxi DressesFormal DressesLong Sleeve DressesSeamless DressesWrap DressesCasual Dresses Jumpsuits & Rompers TopsCrop TopsTank Tops BottomsSkirtsShortsDenim ShortsPants & Leggings ActivewearSports BrasActive TopsActive ShortsActive PantsAthleisure
Shop By CategoryYandy Bra CollectionBralettesDD-F CupDemi Cup BrasLingerie BrasLongline BrasOpen Cup BrasPadded BrasPlus Size BrasPush-Up BrasSheer BrasShelf BraSports BrasStrapless Bras
Shop By CategoryShop All HosieryGarter StockingsKnee High StockingsThigh High StockingsSeamed StockingsStriped StockingsPantyhoseSeamed PantyhoseSeamless PantyhoseSheer PantyhoseSocksAnklets
Shop By CategoryShop All Panties10 For $35 PantiesBikiniBoyshortsCrotchless PantiesG-StringsHipsterThongsSide Tie PantiesSeamless Panties
Trending ShopsYandy Panty of the Day
Shop By CategoryDancewear AccessoriesDancewear BodysuitsDancewear BottomsDancewear DressesDancewear SetsDancewear TopsLeggingsGlow In The Dark ClothingNeon OutfitsPride ClothingCall Her 6 Drag CollectionRave ClothingRave Costumes
Shop By CategoryShop All SwimwearBikinisMicro BikinisMix & Match SwimsuitsOne Piece SwimsuitsPlus Size SwimwearPool FloatsResort SwimSwim BottomsSwim TopsSwimwear Cover-Ups
Trending ShopsThe Swim Edit2020 Swimwear Collection
Shop By Category3" Heels4" Heels5" Heels6" Heels & HigherBootsThigh High BootsKnee High BootsBootiesCostume ShoesEvening ShoesFashion ShoesFlatsMary JanesPlatformPumpsSandalsSlidesStripper HeelsWedge
Best Selling CostumesShop All Sexy Halloween CostumesNew For 2020Exclusive CostumesPlus Size CostumesMen's CostumesSexy Men's CostumesDIY Costume ShopCostumes Under $30Halloween Lounge & Rompers2020 Halloween LookbookPet CostumesSale! CostumesAnimal CostumesBunny CostumesCop CostumesCostume AccessoriesCouples CostumesFrench Maid CostumesNinja CostumesNurse CostumesPirate CostumesSchool Girl CostumesWitch Costumes
Shop By CategoryAlice in Wonderland CostumesAngel CostumesArmy CostumesBeer Girl CostumesCat CostumesCheerleader CostumesCircus CostumesCosplay CostumesDorothy CostumesEgyptian CostumesFairy CostumesFirefighter CostumesFlapper CostumesGangster CostumesGenie CostumesGreek Gods & Goddess CostumesGypsy CostumesLion CostumesLion Tamer CostumesLittle Red Riding Hood CostumesMen's CostumesMermaid CostumesMilitary CostumesMinnie Mouse CostumesPrincess CostumesQueen of Hearts CostumesReferee CostumesSWAT CostumesSailor CostumesScary CostumesSkeleton CostumesSports CostumesSteampunk CostumesSuperhero CostumesTinkerbell CostumesUnicorn CostumesVampire CostumesWarrior CostumesWizard of Oz CostumesZombie Costumes
Shop By CategoryShop All Sale - Up to 90%LingerieCostumesBrasDressesSwimwearActivewearHosieryPantiesDancewear
Special Deals10 For $35 Panties3 For $39 BrasLast Chance / Clearance!2 for $22 Bralettes
Shop By CategoryPlus Size BabydollsPlus Size Bedroom CostumesPlus Size Body ShapersPlus Size BodystockingsPlus Size BodysuitsPlus Size Bridal LingeriePlus Size BustiersPlus Size Camisole SetsPlus Size ChemisesPlus Size CorsetsPlus Size Crotchless LingeriePlus Size Exotic LingeriePlus Size Fishnet LingeriePlus Size Gartered LingeriePlus Size Leather LingeriePlus Size Open Cup LingeriePlus Size Pajamas & SleepwearPlus Size RobesPlus Size TeddiesPlus Size Vinyl & Latex LingeriePlus Size Waist Cinchers
Trending ShopsHoliday Lingerie2020 Holiday Gift GuideYandy Vixens ShopWork From Home WardrobeYandy 101: The Ultimate Guide
Shop By CategoryPlus Size Cover-upsPlus Size Mix & Match SwimsuitsPlus Size One Piece SwimsuitsPlus Size Sexy BikinisPlus Size TankinisPlus Size Two Piece Swimsuits
Shop By CategoryPlus Size ClubwearPlus Size Cocktail DressesPlus Size Dancewear Sets
Shop By CategoryPlus Size Bra SetsPlus Size BralettesPlus Size Demi Cup BrasPlus Size Padded BrasPlus Size Sports Bras
Shop By CategoryPlus Size Garter StockingsPlus Size PantyhosePlus Size Thigh High Stockings
Shop By CategoryPlus Size Bikini PantiesPlus Size BoyshortsPlus Size G-StringsPlus Size High Waisted PantiesPlus Size HipsterPlus Size ThongsPlus Size Crotchless Panties
Shop By CategoryPlus Size Active WearPlus Size Halter TopsPlus Size RompersPlus Size ShortsPlus Size SkirtsPlus Size TopsFace Masks
Shop By CategoryPlus Size Alice In Wonderland CostumesPlus Size Character CostumesPlus Size Fairytale CostumesPlus Size French Maid CostumesPlus Size Mens CostumesPlus Size Movie & TV CostumesPlus Size School Girl CostumesPlus Size Sexy Animal CostumesPlus Size Sexy Cop CostumesPlus Size Sexy Nurse CostumesPlus Size Sexy Sports CostumesPlus Size Sexy Witch Costumes
